That's Jonas's signal.
He rang it last night, too.
Did he finish another piece?
Hmm. All right.
I'll use
my investigative prowess.
I added some more
folds to her dress.
And I put open work
detail on the hems.
It's much more accurate
than before. What did
you find out? Mithril.
Huh? So it's you. I caught him
trying to enter Jonas's room,
so I grabbed him before
he could do anything dubious.
Brute! How dare you accuse me?
I was
only going to play
one small prank on him.
A prank? He looked
incredibly depressed, so that's
great for us. What? I wonder
why. Don't come a day. You.
Is it finished? Yes, I gave it
my best. Then we should
signal too. Right? Would you?
There's no change.
It's the same as yesterday.
You know.
You and that boy downstairs.
You two don't understand
a thing. Now give it form.
What does he mean?
I added details,
but he said it hadn't changed.
What's wrong with it?
Perhaps the Duke
of Felix is looking
for something more than a
splendid sugar confection. Hmm.
If that were all he wanted, then
your work would have been
more than sufficient.
This time.
Let's try approaching it from
a different direction.
Maybe more realistic.
This one looks a lot different.
Is it finished now? Yes.
But I want to take one more
look at the art
before I show him.
I have to see the Duke. Aw.
Oh, I just want to see
the paintings again. Haha.
So you're still working
on a piece? Yes. Aren't you?
I can't make anything. I don't
understand what he's looking for.
No matter how he describes it.
It makes me want to quit.
Well, I can't say that wouldn't
help me if you did that, but.
That may be how you feel
right now. But just you wait.
He's bruised.
What is that?
No, this is all wrong.
What is it that's wrong?
Everything. But how?
I'm sorry,
but that can't be true.
I've checked the paintings
countless times to make sure.
And yet you still haven't
succeeded. This is a mockery.
I can't even look at it.
You will give it form.
If it's the last thing you do.
Pull yourself together an.
The Duke. He did this?
That's right.
It's pointless. No matter how many you
make, you won't be satisfied.
It's time for
us to leave this place.
You're suggesting that we
give up? I am.
Me too. It seems like
it's our only option now.
Shame about the thousand crests.
But.
Give up on the work.
But I said I'd do it.
Some things are just impossible.
You know.
What he's after
could be something that can't
be captured as a sugar
confection. Something unattainable.
Huh? No, Chale, it can't be.
Otherwise
he wouldn't have had
that look on his face.
I have to keep on trying.
I'm sorry I made you to worry.
Hmm.
Michelle, why don't
you take the bed tonight?
I don't mind sleeping
on the floor.
I refuse Mithra.
Lid pod is snoring too loudly.
So, have you always
been this bitter?
Well, after living for
a hundred years,
anyone who isn't bitter
is just naive. A hundred?
Although if it were you,
you might stay the same.
What does that mean?
It makes sense though.
Shell has been
around for 100 years.
I'm sure he's met a lot
of people. And of course.
Say that list, girl. What was
she like? Was she beautiful?
Indeed. She was beautiful.
What color are her eyes?
Was her hair long? Was she kind?
She had bright blue eyes.
Her hair was long.
And more than being kind.
She was mature.
She thought much more
than she spoke.
Is that so?
She was the opposite of me.
I'm not pretty.
I'm childish, I'm loud.
And I rarely
think before I speak.
What's wrong?
Huh?
Huh? Where did that come from?
Did I say something
that was upsetting to you?
No, not at all.
Excuse me, I think
I have something in my eye.
I'll go wash my face.
Honestly,
what is the matter with me?
I should apologize to shell.
Why is the door open? Shall.
Hello, Anne. What is this?
Why are you in my room?
So tell me,
do you recognize this? Swing.
And I'm sorry. I was asleep and.
Ah! Stop it now!
Leave him alone.
I'm the one you
really want to hurt.
There's nothing I want
to do to you.
But there's something that I'd
like you to do for me. What?
Man, you're going to say
this to Chale.
I don't want you here anymore.
Leave
this castle now and never show your
face around me again. Clear.
I'd never do something
like that. No!
Stop crushing it. Do as I say,
and I'll gladly give it back.
But if you breathe a word
about this to shul,
then I'll rip it to pieces.
Charles. Why?
I didn't expect that.
Asking about
Liz and then starting to cry.
It doesn't make sense.
So you came back.
Shall I have something to say?
I want you to leave here.
Hmm'hmm.
To sleep in a different room.
No, I meant leave the castle.
And never
show your face around me again.
Ever.
Are you saying you don't want
to stay together anymore?
Why? It isn't your fault. Shall.
It's mine.
I'm sorry,
but please don't ask questions.
As you wish.
That was wonderfully sad, an.
Why would you make me do this?
Give me the wing.
Not yet.
Tomorrow, you and I will
go visit the Duke of Phylax.
I'll speak and you will go along
with everything I say
without complaint.
Follow all of my instructions
to the letter.
What are you planning to do?
You'll see tomorrow, won't you?
I'm sorry. This is my fault. No.
Only Jonas is in the wrong.
But you had
to do that to the person
you love.
It's not like that.
Don't try to hide it.
What makes you
think you can fool
me? You do, don't you?
So.
Perhaps.
Everything ends this way.
Suddenly and harshly.
Where should I go now?
Looks like a quality
companion fairy.
Whoa, wait. I think he's
a warrior type. Either way.
It'll sell for a high price.
You've
caught me in an awful mood.
Don't blame me if you die.
Yah yah yah yah!
That's enough, Shao Feng Shao.
If you
kill any humans,
then I can't protect you.
As for you lot, if you run away,
I'll pretend I didn't see this.
If it isn't the layabout Viscount.
You're as charming as ever.
At least pretend you're
thankful I saved your life.
So where are the other two?
Tell me what you're
doing here first. Ah.
I have some business
at Phylax Castle,
and you probably just
came from there, right?
No matter since we've
crossed paths. You should come
with me.
But Duke's in serious danger.
Why are you here? I've come
to ask you for a favor.
Now an remember,
you can't oppose me at all.
Do exactly as I tell you.
Or else
I ask that you set
me free of my work here.
Isn't that what you asked
me for the other day? Yes.
And what did I tell you that
time? The quitting. Is forbidden.
Correct. Trying to escape.
And I'll put you in chains.
I said that as well.
But if you've forgotten,
then this pain will remind you.
Don't ask me again. Wait.
That bruise. Have mercy. I can't
make anything else, your Grace.
But Anne will stay
here in my stead.
She'll work until you have the.
Perfect
sugar confection and no
one will argue.
I even drove her warrior
fairy away. So please allow.
Me to leave.
I'm of no use to you anymore.
I've heard quite enough. Please, I'm begging
you. Don't hear me anymore.
You look just like your Grace.
He's telling you the truth.
What? I'll
make you the peace you want,
whatever it takes.
So please allow Jonas to leave.
Whatever it takes.
Yes. I won't let
you depart from this castle until
you succeed. That's all. Right.
I promised you I'd do this,
so I'll keep going.
I see. Then you'll make it
without fail.
How could you make
a promise like that?
We both know he's
never satisfied with anything.
Well, unlike you,
I prefer to finish
what I start. And I will.
There's something deeply wrong with
you. Definitely. She's stupid.
What do you want? It's time for
you to give back my thrills.
Wing. All right. Of course.
Goodbye. I'll make it happen somehow. Because
after all, it's my work.
I know why she made you leave.
It's that sour look on your
face. Feet on the table. Lovely.
This is tiresome. I understand
this is troubling you.
What is this danger that brings
you to the Duke's castle?
There's a smell
of smoke about things,
and the fact that Anne
is still there distresses me.
For a year and a half. The Duke
of Felix hasn't been seen
in Lewiston at all.
Do you know what that means?
He hasn't been demonstrating fealty to the
royal family. Is that right?
I don't know the reason.
Regardless, the Earl
of Downing finds it unforgivable
and called for his subjugation.
In the end, His Majesty was
pressured into permitting it.
So if we don't act now,
the Earl's
going to bring
his soldiers to Felax.
And I want to prevent
the Duke from being killed.
In the days
before I was Viscount.
I used to visit
him quite frequently.
So I could make
sugar confections for
the woman who was at his side.
That's why I know
the Duke's nature so well.
Trust me, he has no ambitions.
It's been a long time,
your Grace.
Why have you come here?
Please come with me to Lewiston.
So that's it? I refuse. But it
could be fun. You call that fun?
The truth is,
the Earl of Downing
and his forces are on their way.
But His Majesty doesn't wish
for your subjugation.
It's not too late for you.
Please come.
I told you I'm not going.
I know. Why don't you bring
Lady Christina along with you?
She enjoyed Lewiston,
didn't she? Yes.
That's an excellent idea.
Get out!
I order you to leave.
What's upsetting you,
your Grace. No one
can give me commands and no one
makes decisions for me.
Is that clear? Mercury.
Uh, my neck is so stiff.
Oh. The pain. Uh.
I'm sorry, but you could have
waited back in the room.
Don't be absurd.
How could you have
gotten here without my brilliant
guidance? Mm. That's true.
So why do you think it has
to be her? Mm, I couldn't say.
There must be some reason.
Huh?
Wait a minute.
Why didn't I notice it before?
She has both her wings.
Which means that this fairy has
never been made to serve anyone.
Why does he have her portrait
if she didn't work here?
Perhaps the Duke
of Felix is looking
for something more than
a splendid sugar confection.
I know, I have to ask
his grace about this fairy.
You can't be serious.
He's clearly lost his mind.
It's not safe to confront him.
What
if you get hurt like Jonas did?
Actually, Mr. Lippert, I think
that you should leave here too.
What? I can't abandon you.
There's no
need to put you in danger. This
is my work, after all. So I'm
the only one who has to stay.
And I'll come find you as
soon as I finish the piece.
All right. Fine.
I guess I'll leave the castle.
But the only reason I'm doing it
is to locate Shell and Shell.
That way I can tell him you
didn't mean all those things
you said to him.
Leave it to my superior genius.
All right, then, it's up to you.
Heh. I can do it.
I have to go see the Duke.